

# ADITI PRIYA WEB DEVELOPER

- +916200964848
- ≥ aditipriya460@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/aditi-priya-33095a273/

Pursuing my passion for education. I am a Computer Science Engineering student from Government Engineering College, Ramgarh. Programming and making new interesting websites related to my interest excites me and I am always up for grabbing new information about the things I like. Certain skills that I have worked with include Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJs, MySQL) & Artificial Intelligence (Python). And what I might lack in skills I make up for with my determination to learn.

# **Experience**

#### Student Coordinator at REC Student Portal

May 2023-Present

- UDAAN was the only official group of Ramgarh Engineering College created and managed by the students of REC till 2023.
- REC STUDENT PORTAL (website of UDAAN) is the one-stop destination for every college related informations like important notice, question papers, results and much more.
- It even conducts some events on regular intervals like quizathon, codewar, gusto etc.

#### Student Member at BOSCH India

May 2023-0ct-23

- BOSCH acts in an economically, environmentally, and socially responsible manner, they want to improve people's quality of life and safeguard the livelihoods of present and future generations.
- The YES programme run by BOSCH India encourages corporates to contribute to empowerment in areas of national priority.
- It trains the individual in 4 different lifesytle aspects.

#### Nurturing Ambassador at BIS Club, REC

June 2023-Present

- BIS is the National Standard Body of India for the harmonious development of the activities of standardization, marking and quality certification of goods and for matters connected therewith or incidental thereto.
- As a Nurturing Ambassador, I work as the public face for BIS Club running in REC.
- My primary duties include creating awareness among people about their day to day rights and about the things going in the world.

#### Event Manager at Aarambh:Imagination Leads to Automation!

October 2023-Present

- Aarambh is one of the official group of Ramgarh Engineering College created and managed by the students of REC.
- Aarambh:Imagination leads to Automation! is the one-stop destination for every Automation/IOT related informations .
- It has just started but is looking forward to bring various technical events like tech-fest, seminars by well known personalities in the field of robotics, hackathons etc,

### **Education**

#### **Government Engineering College**

- · Bachelor of Engineering
- Major in Computer Science Engineering

#### **PVSS DAV Public School**

- Intermediate
- Major in Science with PCM with percentage of 90%

#### Modern Public School

- Matriculation
- Percentage: 90.8%

# Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- C Programming
- Python

- Leadership
- Team Management
- Communication
- · Public Speaking
- · Problem Solving

# **Project**

#### Portfolio Project

Project link:- https://adii-190.github.io/portfolio/

#### **Personal Site**

Project link:- https://adii-1906.github.io/html-personal.site/

# Certificates

#### Certificate of Internship - Artificial intelligence

- Campalin Innovations
- Issued: June 2023
- Credential ID CAMP 2704

#### Certificate of Completion - Web Development

- Udemy
- Issued: June 2023
- Credential ID: UC-4a63f967-bf44-449b-b314-57cf885cd775Credential ID UC-4a63f967-bf44-449b-b314-57cf885cd775

#### Certificate of Participation - Backend development

- DevTown
- Issued: July 2023
- Credential ID: https://cert.devtown.in/verify/Z1T8Y5X

Dec 2022-Present

June 2019-April2021

August 2006-April 2019

#### **Certificate of Appreciation**

- DevTown
- Issued: July 2023
- Credential ID: https://cert.devtown.in/verify/Z5XQPu

#### Microsoft certified Student Ambassador

- DevTown
- Issued: July 2023
- Credential ID: https://cert.devtown.in/verify/Z1rEazT

#### Certificate of Completion - C problem solving

- CodeChef
- Issued: Sep 2023
- Credential ID: 1a6795c Username: aditipriya460

#### Certificate of Completion - C(Programming language)

- CodeChef
- Issued: Sep 2023
- Credential ID: 6d2de12 Username: aditipriya460

#### Certificate of Participation

- OpenWeaver
- Issued: Sep 2023
- Credential ID: 89187699269186

#### Certification of Completion with Excellence(Web Development)

- Programming Hero
- Skills:- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, DOM
- Credential Id: PH1293

#### Certification of Completion with Excellence(C Programming)

- Programming Hero
- Skills:- C(Basic+DSA+OOP)
- Credential Id: PH1293

#### Certification of Completion with Excellence(C++ Programming)

- Programming Hero
- Skills:- C++(Basic+DSA+OOP)
- Credential Id: PH1293

#### Certification of Completion with Excellence(React JS)

- Programming Hero
- Skills:- React JS, jsx
- Credential Id: PH1293

#### Courses

## Artificial Intelligence (Python)

- Campalin Innovation
- Major in Artificial Intelligence, Major in Python.

# Web Development

- Udemy
- Major in Full Stack Web Development.

April 2023-May-2023

May 2023-June 2023